當我大聲喊，你能否聽到？
Can you hear my voice when I call out?
跟以前比起來，有什麼新的？
Is there something new from what before?
經歷了這麼多，我能否喘口氣？
Can I get a break from everything I've gone through?
你也可以看看活了多久
You can use that lifetime too
太多雙翅膀，太多匹在飛翔
Way too many wings, too many up on high
每一雙翅膀，就有隻角
and for every pair, there's a horn
魔法大家有
Magic's got to spare
感覺能做的還有好多
Feel like I could be so much more
就做什麼
Do anything
彷彿能夠—
Feel like I could--
—打倒一隻大熊座
--take down an Ursa Major
能抬起這個該死世界
like I could lift up the whole damn world
但我能否就停止作夢
But can I get a break from dreaming
他媽對一個女孩還是太多
it's just too much for one damn girl
歷史是給那些不好好玩的人來寫
History is written by the ones who don't play nice
守規矩的人不會有什麼聲望
No fame is gained in behaving
要是能達成目的我也會開始動亂
I'd start a riot if it meant I'd get my way
聽聽看在那新暑期中的魔力
Listen for the magic in the new type summer phase
登上舞台，把握時機
You take the stage and seize the moment
翻過一頁，聽見海聲
Turn a page and hear the ocean
燒一座橋，再建新的
We burn a bridge and then rebuild it
就算是鹹魚，也能夠翻身
Not one c-list protag gone amiss
太多雙翅膀，太多匹在飛翔
Way too many wings, too many up on high
每一雙翅膀，就有隻角
and for every pair, there's a horn
魔法大家有
Magic's got to spare
感覺能做的還有好多
Feel like I could be so much more
就做什麼
Do anything
彷彿能夠—
Feel like I could--
—打倒一隻大熊座
--take down an Ursa Major
能抬起這個該死世界
like I could lift up the whole damn world
但我能否就停止作夢
But can I get a break from dreaming
他媽對一個女孩還是太多
it's just too much for one damn girl